(Raj:)Oh, another two hours to go.
(Raj:)The wait
is killing me.
(Howard:)I know. I get it. When I was
in the Soyuz capsule
(Howard:)returning from the space
station, plummeting toward Earth
(Howard:)at 17,000 miles per hour...
Before you finish,
(Raj:)is this a story about
patience and waiting
(Raj:)or just another reminder
that you went to space?
(Howard:)A story can
do two things.
(Raj:)Ugh, I feel like I'm gonna
have a heart attack.
(Howard:)You work in
pharmaceuticals--
(Howard:)don't you have
anything you can give him?
(Bernadette:)All I have is our new
urine flow drug.
(Bernadette:)Won't help with his anxiety,
but it's so strong, when he pees
(Bernadette:)he'll fly around the room
like he's got a jet pack.
(Raj:)I can't stop thinking about it.
(Bernadette:)You know, worrying won't
have any effect on what happens.
(Penny:)I know.
Maybe you need to do
something more productive.
(sighs)
Okay.
(Sheldon:)Ah.
(Raj:)If I make this shot
(Raj:)in the trash can,